目前，所有的列表项都有相同的布局。
Currently, all the list
items have the same layout.
然而，我们希望今日项目使用不同的布局，
However, we want the today
item to use a different layout
也就是我们之前在list_item_forecast_today XML文件中定义的。
which we defined earlier in the list
item forecast today XML file.
这就是适配器项的“项视图类型”发挥作用的地方了。
This is where adapter item
view types will save the day.
这是一个对所有适配器通用的概念，不只是针对CursorAdapter。
This is a general concept for
all adapters, not just cursor adapter.
不再只是知道一个“项视图类型”，来给所有列表项
Instead of just knowing about one item
view type which yields the same layout
产生相同的布局，适配器可以申明多个“项视图类型”，
for all list items, the adapter can
declare multiple item view types, so
这样就可以有多个不同的列表项布局了。
it will have different
list item layouts.
针对游标中给定的一行，天气预报适配器需要决定
For a given row in the cursor,
the forecast adapter needs to decide
他应该是一个普通列表项还是一个今日列表项。
if it should be a regular list item or
a today list item.
然后他就会解析，并且为适当的视图绑定数据。
Then it will inflate, and
bind data for the appropriate layout.
我们现在跳到天气预报适配器的代码来学习如何
We'll jump into the forecast
adapter code now to learn how to
处理第二个“项视图类型”
handle a second item view type.
通常，在子类中，getViewTypeCount返回1，
Normally, in a sub class
getViewTypeCount returns one, but
但是我们将会覆盖他，让他为两个不同的布局返回2。
we're going to override it so it returns
two for the two different layouts.
但是他怎么知道何时使用一个布局何时另一个呢？
But how does it know when to
use one layout, or the other?
我们覆写getItemViewType方法，这样当列表中的位置是
Well we override getItemViewType, so
that when the position in the list is
0那么我们认为那就是今日视图类型。
zero then we say that
it's the today view type.
否则，就是FUTURE_DAY视图类型。
Otherwise, it's
the FUTURE_DAY view type.
这两种视图类型在上面声明好。
These two view types
are declared up above.
他们就只是代表了视图类型的整形。
These are just integer
representations of the view type.
数字必须从0开始，因为这些值不能大于
The numbering has to start at 0, because
these values cannot be greater than or
或等于getViewTypeCount。
equal to getViewTypeCount.
所以我们的位置值是0和1，这样我们知道0总是映射
So the possible values for us are 0 and
1, so that we know that 0 always maps
到VIEW_TYPE_TODAY，1始终映射到VIEW_TYPE_FUTURE_DAY。
to the view_type_today, and that one
always maps to view_type_future_day.
我们将要在newView方法中使用这一信息。
We're going to use this information
in the new view method.
记住之前，我们初始化了list_item_forecast XML。
Remember that previously,
we inflated the list item forecast xml.
现在我们将要使用“项视图类型”来判断我们应该使用
Now we're going to use item view type
to determine whether we should use one
某一布局或另一个。
layout or the other.
填写TODO来实现这一行为。
Fill in the TODO to
address this behavior.
layoutID表示resourceID
LayoutID refers to resourceID
其形式是R.layout.xxx
which is in the form of r
dot layout dot something.